

Spring 2013 Nominated Officer Questionnaire

PART I: GENERAL INFORMATION

Name: Tiffany Dayemo Year: Sophomore Major: Pledge Class (Year): Omega (Spring 2012)	
Please mark which elected position(s) you are r	unning for with an X:
[] President [] Pledgemaster [] VP of Service [] VP of Membership	[] VP of Fellowship[] VP of Finance[] VP of Communications[X] Fundraising Chair

PART II: SHORT ANSWER QUESTIONS

- What is your vision for APO? My vision for Alpha Phi Omega is a community that dedicates a
 lifetime of service not only to the community but also to its fellow members by being there for
 each other like true brothers. I want to see the organization grow its presence on campus and
 reach out to an even more diverse group of students.
- 2. Why do you want the position(s) you are running for?

I would like the position of Fundraising Chair because I believe it's a position that will push me to find creative ways to organize and help fundraise for an organization I really care about.

- 3. What are your goals for the position(s)?
- Create and stick to more local and on campus fundraisers to reduce gas costs and make it more convenient for members and their friends to come out.
- Plan ahead accordingly to ensure smoothly run fundraisers
- Stick to One big fundraiser per month, and then smaller fundraisers such as Yogurtland, Viztango's etc.
- 4. What new ideas can you bring to the position and organization as a whole? Please provide examples.

-Some examples of ideas I'd like to bring are selling bracelets or fashionable hand made merchandise that students on campus would want to buy but aren't expensive to make. The process of making them could help brothers bond as well.

- Sundae Nights/ Themed food nights once a month where members would pay a few bucks to enjoy unlimited food.
- IC Fundraiser Karaoke Night/Performance where you could pay to hear someone (or more) sing/dance and you can choose their song.
- 5. What relevant experience, if any, have you had working in committees or other organizations for the position(s) you are running for? Please be specific.

I have been in the Fundraising committee for two semesters in a row since pledging, so I understand the process that goes into fundraising for APO as well as working with other members to help set up fundraisers. I also am currently Alpha Family Head so I have experience planning events and coordinating with family heads other e-board members for events. I am also pretty good at consistently updating family members on Facebook and e-mail, and being clear on everything I plan (transparency)

6. What other time commitments will you have next semester (i.e. Other student organizations, work, research, etc.)? How do you plan to balance APO executive board duties with those commitments?

I will have a job, as well as be moderately involved in Model UN. I think I can balance them because my Fridays are currently free and I will only work 5 hours a week. My main priority, if elected, will be my position as fundraising chair.

Tiffany Kassamo Dayemo

3032 Winners Circle ● Charleston, SC 29414● 843-737-3541 ● dayemo@usc.edu

EDUCATION

University of Southern California, Los Angeles, CA Bachelor of Arts, International Relations and Spanish GPA 3.48

May 2015

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Office of the Vice Provost of Faculty Affairs, Los Angeles, CA March 2012-June 2012 Receptionist

Greet guests of the Vice Provost, organize faculty files, and answer phone calls.

Teaching International Relations Program, Los Angeles, CA

January 2012- May 2012

Tutor/Mentor

- Plan comprehensive lessons for high school students in public schools to teach them about international relations, and ethical issues that impact the global community.
- Use interactive, and current issues as tools to engage students in the material
- Submit evaluations from the student's teachers, as well as our own experience to professors and staff.

McNair Law Firm, Charleston, SC

May 2010-June 2010

Attorney Intern

- Worked on organizing agendas for Charleston County School Board, and reading on educational law with Chairwoman, Attorney Tova Green
- Met with special interest groups who met with Chairwoman Green, and took observatory notes.

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

Model United Nations @ SC Conference

2012

Co-Chair

Co-chair the United Nations Human Rights Council's session on the Syrian Conflict hosted at the University of Southern California.

Alpha Phi Omega (Community Service Fraternity), Los Angeles, CA

2012

Active Member, Alpha Family Head

- Organize family events around Los Angeles for Active Members to bond in brotherhood
- Raised \$400 in a school wide fundraiser with pledge class
- Worked with other service oriented programs such as Skid Row and Angel's Flight in the inner city LA area to better serve the community

Explore USC, Los Angeles, CA

2011-Present

Scholar Mentor and Host

Host prospective students for USC Trustee and Presidential Scholar Program, and act as their guide during their time at USC.

SKILLS

Proficient in Spanish, Latin, Ancient Greek. Conversational: Italian Languages: Software:

Proficient in MS Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint) and Adobe Photoshop

ACTIVITIES/AWARDS

Alpha Lambda Delta National Honor Society: 2012

Alpha Phi Omega: 2012

H. Roe Bartle Award (Alpha Phi Omega): Committing more that 50 hours of service in a semester (55 hours)

USC Presidential Scholarship: 2011-Present Model United Nations: 2011-Present

Africa SC: 2012

